{
    "id": "2fdb32a4c7124fb5ab012369c36ac3ba",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the building ....................... is going to be demolished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ........................ reached me yesterday was sent by my mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I met my uncle .......................... had just returned from Africa.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ............................ Jack built it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ......................... were watching the match clasped heartily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ........................ tells lies deserves to be punished.",
            "description": "Either who or that is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard some news ................................ astonished me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a man ............................ wears prosthetic legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me the book ......................... is on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We boarded a bus ....................... was full of people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a friend ...................... is a clever artist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a well-known man ....................... generosity is the talk of the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}